After a long winter, the arrival of spring can be a welcome relief.
经过漫长的冬天，春天的到来是一种令人愉快的慰藉。
The days grow longer, the temperatures increase, and the natural world around us comes to life again.
白天变长，气温升高，我们周围的自然世界再次复苏。
But when the seasons change, our sleep patterns change with them.
但当季节变化时，我们的睡眠模式也随之改变。
New research suggests that humans may need more sleep in the winter than they do in the summer.
新研究表明，人类在冬天可能比夏天需要更多睡眠。
A German study found that participants slept an hour longer in December than in June, regardless of their exposure to light.
德国一项研究发现，实验参与者在十二月的睡眠时间比六月长一小时，无论他们接触光照的情况如何。"
"Our study shows that even while living in an urban environment, with just artificial light, humans [experience] seasonal sleep," says Dieter Kunz, one of the study's lead authors and head of the clinic of sleep and chronomedicine at St Hedwig Hospital in Berlin, Germany.
我们的研究表明，即使生活在城市环境中，只有人造光，人类也会经历季节性睡眠，"该研究的主要作者之一、德国柏林圣赫德维格医院睡眠与时间医学诊所主任迪特尔·孔茨说。
The study found that the participants experienced seasonal variations in their rapid eye movement sleep, also known as REM sleep, as well as in their slow wave sleep, also known as deep sleep.
研究发现，参与者的快动眼睡眠以及慢波睡眠（也称为深度睡眠）都存在季节性变化。
REM sleep, which is when we dream and our heart rate increases, was 30 minutes longer in the winter than during the summer.
快动眼睡眠是我们做梦、心率加快的阶段，冬季比夏季长30分钟。
Slow wave sleep, which is when our muscles are repaired, our immune system is strengthened and our memory is consolidated, was 30 minutes shorter in September than in February.
慢波睡眠是我们的肌肉得到修复、免疫系统得到加强、记忆得到巩固的阶段，九月比二月短30分钟。
But why do our bodies and brains need more rest at certain times of year?
但为什么我们的身体和大脑在一年中的某些时候需要更多休息哪？
The answer could lie in our evolutionary past.
答案可能在于我们的进化史。
That's according to Neil Stanley, who's a sleep expert at Sleep Station, an online provider of cognitive behavioural therapy for insomnia.
睡眠站（一家提供失眠认知行为疗法的在线机构）的睡眠专家尼尔·斯坦利就是这么认为的。"
"We have evolved to dark-light cycles, so when we wake up on a winter's morning and it's dark, our brain is going 'I can't do anything… there's no point leaping out of bed.'"
我们已经进化到适应明暗周期，所以当我们在冬天的早晨醒来，天还黑着的时候，我们的大脑就会想'我什么都做不了……跳下床毫无意义。
Particularly in summer, temperature also plays a role – our bodies require a skin temperature of between 31-35 degrees centigrade for a good night's sleep, but this can be harder to control during the warmer months.
'"尤其是在夏天，温度也起作用——我们的身体需要体表温度在31到35摄氏度之间才能睡个好觉，但在较暖和的月份，这更难控制。
Of course, nowadays, it is our school and work times – not the Sun – that determine when we get up in the morning.
当然，如今决定我们早上几点起床的是我们的上学和工作时间——而不是太阳。
But, as autumn approaches, it seems we now have a good excuse for an early night.
但是，随着秋天临近，我们现在似乎有了早睡的好借口。